(Sheldon:)There's someone at my door.
(Amy:)That doesn't interest me.
Good-bye.
- Can I sleep here tonight?
- Why?
(Raj:)Leonard's having
astronomically inaccurate
Star Trek sex with my sister.
(Sheldon:)I can see how that would be
upsetting. Come in.
(Sheldon:)I'll get the sheets
and blankets for the couch.
(Raj:)Oh, don't bother.
I'll just sleep in Leonard's room.
(Sheldon:)No, I can't authorize that.
(Raj:)Well, he's in my bed.
Why can't I be in his?
(Sheldon:)The Hammurabic Code is
"an eye for an eye,"
not "a bed for a bed."
(Raj:)Come on, dude, I'm exhausted,
and Tyra Banks says
(Raj:)the most important item in your
makeup bag is
(Raj:)a good night's sleep.
(Sheldon:)All right.
(Sheldon:)This is a form
indemnifying me
(Sheldon:)from your use of
"Leonard's bedroom."
(Sheldon:)Sign here, indicating
that I tried to stop you
(Sheldon:)and did so using
a stern facial expression.